Lipsky, David, Papers /4077
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
David Lipsky Papers
1982-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lipsky, David
/4077
27.5 cubic feet
27.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
7980448
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 12, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3012: Alice Cook Papers /4174m: ILR School Minority Report on the 1995 Strategic Planning /4189 OH: ILR School External Relations Office Oral History Interviews /4297: ILR School Biography Files 5780/203: ILGWU Jay Mazur Papers 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files
Lipsky, David B., 1939-
7980448
- Black Unionists, 1941-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Buffalo, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Transfer: Buffalo to Ithaca, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Human Resources Research Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Area Symposium, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Macro-Manpower Com., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- CHOICE - D.B. Lipsky, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- H.I.R.E., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CB Workshop, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Jamestown Proposal (12/74), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILO Governing Body Turin Center, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Symposium Apr. 1969 Buffalo (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Jamestown Labor Management Committee Spr. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Manpower Research Proposal - 1972, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Minority Employment, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Advisory Committee Public Employment, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Affirmative Action Program, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Arbitrator Development Program Robert H. Basso, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- a2T Conference = Summer 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Audio Visual Center, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Computer Services information, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ILR AD HOC. Com. To Examine Student Support Services, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Manpower - Other Colleges, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Extension, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Forum - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- HAP Committee Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Recruiting, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Undergraduate Program Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Labor College Questionnaire 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Long Range Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Department of Collective Bargaining Conference Meeting 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Labor Advisory Comm. 1971 - List (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Graduate Study in Manpower flyer (NYSSILR), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- New Dean - Search Comm., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Cornell, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Planning Committee (1970) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Labor Studies Program in N.Y.C. (Assoc. Degree), 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Manpower Seminar- 1971 (Robert. Aronson), 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Planning Committee (1973) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Undergraduate Program Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ILR and Urban Affairs Program (Extension- N.Y.C.), 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Alumni Reunion, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Junior Semester in NYC, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Rejected Papers, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- ILR Library Committee, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Labor Management Documentation Center, 1963-1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- ILR Graduate Faculty, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Collect. Barg. Dept. Conference - Oct. 1970 "Barg. In Private Sect." (Box 3, Folder 6)
- "Contract Administration in Higher Education" Seminar Oct. 16-17, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Pete Doeringer, (Harvard Univ.), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- "Economics of Barg." March 17, 1972 -Ext. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Equal Opportunity Comm. Hearings; IRA Sessions; General Motors Article; Minority Employment Seminar; Labor Productivity Conference, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Nat'l Science Found. Consulting 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- NEA Research - Teacher Strikes (1969-1973) (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Niagara Frontier Manage. Conference- May 1970, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- NYS Symposium on Public Sector Bargaining (Robert Helsby, 5/74), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Project Consultant 5/72, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Research Needs on Fact-Finding in Public Sector, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Safety Project 1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Search Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- DBL 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Search Committee File 2, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Publications Division, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- ORI, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Courses - ILR 200 Spring 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Courses - ILR 200 Spring 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Courses - ILR 200(300) Fall 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Courses - ILR 200(300) Fall 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Courses - ILR 346 Spring 1971-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Courses - ILR 400 Spring 1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Courses - ILR 401 Fall 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Courses - ILR 405 Fall 1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Courses - ILR 500(700), 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Courses - ILR 550 Spring 1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Courses - ILR 687 Student Papers Fall: 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Courses - ILR 609 Fall 1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Role of the Employer in the Rention of Hardcore Trainees -DBL, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- OJT, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- OJT, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- DBL-"Some Correlates of Trainee Success in Coupled OJT Program", 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- "Union Attitudes Towards Significant Aspects of Job Training Programs for the Disadvantaged", 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- The Use if Impasse Procedures in Public School Negotiations, 1952-1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Taylor Law Impasse Albany, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Reprints Orders, Letters to Publishers, reprints sent out.. 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- DBL, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Abstracts - Ch. Gold of Articles-DBL 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- "Analysis of Impasse Procedure in Public Sector Negotiation Research Needs & Hypothesis, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- "Black Workers & The Building Trades: Case of Project JUSTICE", 1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Collective Negotiations in the Public Sector, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Correlates of Employer Participation in Job Training, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Manpower Training Programs for Hardcore Disadvantaged, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Guaranteed Annual Income: Bibliography, 1965-1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Effects of Col. Bargaining on Public School Teachers Salaries: Comment", 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- "The Influence of Collective Bargaining on Teachers' Salaries, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- D. - Abstract. "Interplant Transfer & Terminated Workers", 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- JUSTICE- "Black Workers & the Building Trades", 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Black Workers and the Building Trades (Box 6, Folder 14)
- PERB Study - 1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Thesis' and Applications 1983 Surnames A to G (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Thesis' and Resumes 1983 Surnames I to S (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Thesis' and Resumes 1983 Surnames S (Box 7, Folder 3)
- DBL Review of Proposal to Nat'l Sci. Found by David. A. Bednar, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Vita Brian E. Becker, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- The Labor Market Experience of Workers Displaced and Relocated by Plant Shutdowns: The General Foods Experience, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Final Offer Arbitration The Commonwealth of Mass 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- M.I.T., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Papers by Lipsky, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- DBL. Farber. - 7/75 Article Draft, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- IRRA Meeting - N.Y.C. 12/28-12/30/77 Recent Developments in Public Sector Bargaining DBL, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Final Arbitration Article Dec. 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- M.I.T. Conf. 3/76, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- DBL. Misc. Correspondents 9/79, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- No.344 The Influence of Collective Bargaining on Teachers' Salaries in New York State, 1968-1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Reprints No. 344 & 345, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Reprints No. 344 & 345 Folder 2, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Interplant Transfer Terminated Workers: A Case Study, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Interplant Transfer and Terminated Workers: A Case Study, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Some Correlates of Trainee Success in a couples on-the-job Training, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  '
- Some Correlates of Trainee Success Folder 2, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Reprints No.344 and No. 345, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Reprints No. 344 and No. 345, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- IRRA 1974 Meetings Winter (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Draft Profile of JET, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- JET Progress Report May 1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- "Interplant Transfer and Displaced Workers in a Coupled OJT Program": DBL (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Factors Related to the Success of Disadvantaged Workers in a Coupled-OJT Program, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Interplant Transfer Dis. Workers: A Case Study: File #2, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Effect of Union Mgt. Safety and Health Committees, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Draft of "Labour Studies Report", 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- The Effectiveness of Union-Mgt. Safety & Health Cmts.: Files #2, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- "The Effectiveness of Union - Mgt. Safety & Health Com. - File # 3, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- "A Survey of Local Union Leaders & Members Attitudes Toward CB, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Strikes, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Union Impact on Plant Safety, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- ABT Work Equity, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Work Equity - ABT, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Productivity Project "QOW", 1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Terry Mulchahey Thesis, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Quality of Work Project Research Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Project JET, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Quality of Work Misc. Material, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Misc. Quality of Work Program, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Construction Program, 1971-1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Zimmerman & Kalkstein Union Security, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Dyer, Lipsky, Kochan Paper, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Dyer, Lipsky, Kochan; Productivity, the Quality of work, and Union Management Cooperation, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Jamestown (was box 10/ff 15), 1975 (Box 10.1, Folder 1)
- Old Exams (From SUNY-Buffalo & MIT) (was box 10/ff 16), 1966-1968 (Box 10.1, Folder 2)
- Construction Strikes (was box 10/ff 17), 1972-1975 (Box 10.1, Folder 3)
- Effectiveness of Union - Management Safety and Health Committees (was box 10/ff 18), 1971-1972 (Box 10.1, Folder 4)
- Jamestown (was box 10/ff 19), 1974 (Box 10.1, Folder 5)
- The Negotiation Process, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Collective Bargaining in the 1970s, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Chapter 5 Wages, Fringe Benefits, and Collective Bargaining, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Chapter 2 The Structure of Collective Bargaining (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Chapter Nonwage issues in Collective Bargaining (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Chapter 7 Collective Bargaining Among Public Sector and While Collar Workers (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Misc., 1973-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Unions and the Nature of Collective Bargaining (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Collective Bargaining, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- ILR 300, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Lecture Notes, 1972-1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- M.I.T. Conference on Labor Cassette Tapes, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  7 Tapes
- Original Typed Ms. Collective Bargaining in the 1970s Dec. 1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- New Directions in Collective Bargaining (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Misc. Material, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Q of W P Sept. 7-8 Minutes, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Reading Lists, 1969-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Memorandums, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Memorandums, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- David Lipsky Papers, Surveys, 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Lipsky School Papers, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Lipsky School Papers and Notes, 1959-1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Lipsky School Notes, M.I.T., 1959-1963 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Lipsky School Notes M.I.T., 1959-1963 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Union Power and Public Policy (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Pierce Memorial Materials, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Notes for "Some Economic Aspects of Immigration, 1783-1870", 1960 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Interindustry Patterns of Worker Protest: A Preliminary Investigation, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Lipsky M.I.T. Notes, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Lipsky School Notes, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Lipsky School Notes, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Lipsky School Notes, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lipsky School Notes, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Lipsky School Notes, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Problem Patterns in Labor Economics; Lipsky, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Trade Union Political Activities; Lipsky (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Misc. Essays, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- 14.121 Homework & Class. Notes, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Manpower Training Evaluation Study, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Factors Related to the Success of Disadvantage. Workers in Coupled-OJT Program, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Buffalo Conference May 1970 "Disadvantage Workers" (Box 14, Folder 3)
- I.R. 3403-DBL Col. Bargain. Buffalo Fall 1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- 14.63: Labor Relations, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Quality of Work Minutes 5/18-5/24-, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Quality of Work Project Expenditures, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Interschool Memos & Res. Advisory Committee Participants, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Ted Mills, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- "Changing Work Ethic" 3/25-27, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Coryell, Ritchie Nat. Sc. Foundation, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- General Correspondence to Participants, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Productivity Research, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Abstract - Prod: Q Of W. P., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Alexander, Mike; Article, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- DBL, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Reimbursement requests and vouchers, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Budget, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Jamestown Site 6/73, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Use of Impasse Procedures in the Public School Negotiations: My Experience", 1971 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Worker Attitudes, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Academic Standards Committee March 1973-Sept. 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Academic Standards Committee Oct. 1974 -Dec. 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Brandeis - Course Articles - Reading, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Brandeis - 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Brandies - 1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Brandeis - 1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Brandeis - 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Brandeis - 1980 Summer Reading Cont. (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Brandeis - 1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Brandeis - 1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Harvard Univ. Inst. 1980 Applications (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Harvard 1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Harvard University Institutes, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Harvard Univ. Inst., 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Evaluation of Rutgers Inst. Mgt. - Labor Rel. 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- MIT Secretaries of Labor Conf. - 3/77 File #1, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- MIT Secretaries of Labor Conf. - 3/77 File #2, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- MIT Secretaries of Labor Conf. - 3/77 File #3, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- MIT Secretaries of Labor Conf. - 3/77 File #4, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Listing of Data for Company, 1969-1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- New PERB Data, 1968-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Salary Data for NYS Schools, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Wilbur Sharpstein Case (Bob Miller), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Teacher-School Board Attitudes (Yuiden)1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Harvard Inst. In Empl. & Training Admin. Proposal - 1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- DBL - Mail 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Agree. Ithaca Teachers & Superintendent. Of Schools Ithaca District, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- File #2 of Ithaca Teachers Assn. Agree., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Owego Appalachian Schools, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Village of Elmira Hgts. Police Benevolent Assn., 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- DeRuyter Central Schools, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Horseheads Teachers, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Schuyler County Deputy Sheriffs, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Schuyler County Deputy Sheriffs, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Kohlers, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Catalog Listings of 1968-1969 SBA Faculty (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Afton Central Schools, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Johnson City Fact Finding, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Charles A. Myers and Harry Chandler, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Personal - DBL, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Kohler #2, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Kohler #3, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Labor Mgt. Committee in Jamestown, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- So. Cayuga Teachers & School District, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Village of Seneca Falls, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Red Creek C. School & Red Creek Faculty Assn., 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Campbell Central School #2 & Campbell Teachers Assn., 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Binghamton City Schools and Binghamton Teachers, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- City of Hornell & Hornell Police Assn., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- DBL - Farber Article July 1975 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- DBL, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Joe Adler Report and Tioga Central School Teachers, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- PERB, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Yates County - PERB, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Afton Central Schools, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Auburn Community College, 6/74, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Deposit Central Sch., 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Village of Johnson City Police Assn., 9/74, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Owego-Appalachian - PERB, July 1974 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Harold R. Newman-PERB, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Arbitrator's Bill (Box 19, Folder 9)
- DBL - Personal, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- DBL - Personal, 1968-1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Binghamton School Teachers, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- DBL - Personal - Binghamton City School District: 1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- DBL - Personal - Binghamton City School District: 1981 Folder #2 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- DBL - Personal Correspondence Binghamton City School District: 1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- DBL - Personal - Drafts Binghamton City School District: 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- DBL - Personal - Cases Binghamton City School District: 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Broome Co. Community College, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Corning Community College, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Cortland County, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- DBL - Personal - Cortland, 1976-1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- DBL - Personal CSEA Dundee Schools, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Hornell Police, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- DBL - Personal - Horseheads Central School District 1981 Folder #1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- DBL - Personal - Horseheads Central School District 1981 Folder #2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Greene BOCES 2, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- DBL - Personal - PERB M75-802 Ithaca School District, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Lansing Teachers, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Maine-Endwell School, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- DBL - Personal - PERB M77-452-New So. Berlin, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- DBL - Personal PERB Norwich - Police, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- DBL - Personal - 1981 Onondaga Central School (Box 21, Folder 1)
- DBL - Personal - 1981 Onondaga CSD Non-In. A. Typed Cases (Box 21, Folder 2)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Seneca Falls School, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- DBL - Personal: 1982 Sherburne-Earville City School District (Box 21, Folder 4)
- DBL - Personal: 1982 Sherburne-Earville City School District Folder #2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Solvay, So. Cayuga, Tioga; DBL, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Union Springs CSEA, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Prattsburg, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- DBL - Personal - Union-Endicott 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- DBL - Personal - PERB Whitesboro & West Genesee C.S.D., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- JET File #1-2, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- JET Files #3-4, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- JET File #5 (Various Proposals), 1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Handouts 1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ILR 300 - Fall 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- ILR #300- Fall 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- ILR - 300 - Fall 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- ILR #300 - Fall 1969 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- ILR #300 - Fall 1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- ILR 100 Spring 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1972 /DBL/ (Box 22, Folder 8)
- ILR #100 - Spring 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- ILR #100 Spr. 1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- ILR 100 - Spring 1969 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- ILR 250 Spring - 1971 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- ILR # 300, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- ILR #400, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- ILR #405, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- ILR # 451 - Spring 1971 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- ILR #500, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- ILR 450 - Vladimir Stoikov Spring 1969 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- ILR #550- Spring 1970 Foltman & Cullen (Box 22, Folder 19)
- ILR 600 - V. Jensen Fall 1973 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- ILR 650 - D. Cullen & F. Foltman, Spring 1975 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- ILR 703 - T. Kochan Spring 1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- ILR 707 - T. Kochan Spring 1975 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Planning #715- Fall 1970 S. Czamanski (Box 22, Folder 24)
- ILR 200 - Mock Barg. Material - 1976 & 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- ILR 200 - Spring 1978 Appendix: CB Ex. + Background Mat. CB Case (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Burns & Bruce Case "The Case of B & B" Lipsky, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- The Case of B & B File #2, 1966-1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- The Case of B & B File # 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- JET File #6, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- JET, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- JET File #7, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- JET Trainees (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Project JET, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Jet Proposal, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- JET - Final Report Phase 1, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- JET - Proposal Phase 3, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- ILR Review Misc. Corres. 1977-79, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- JET Progress Report, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- JET Progress Report, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- JET Correspondence, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- JET Interview Questions, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Background Material for JET, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- JET Related Questionnaire, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- JET Article (Box 24, Folder 11)
- JET Questionnaire, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- JET Tables - Fenwick (Box 24, Folder 13)
- State and Metropolitan Area Unemployment, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- The Employment Situation 1976-1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Related Articles and Tables, 1967-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Original Article and Galley, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Original and Draft (and two copies) REVISED - Sept. 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- The Effect of Teacher Bargaining of Compensation, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Handwritten Original, 1971-1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Computer Printouts (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Abstract & Galley, 1968-1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Draft & Copies Feb. 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Handwritten Draft Oct. 1976 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Original Manuscript and Copies of Article, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Related Articles, 1975-1981 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Tables (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Working Papers Dec. 1976 - Jan. 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Article (Copy) May, 17 1977 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Computer Printouts (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Mass Tax Foundation Criticism on Report, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)